Guide to the Sylvester Manor Archive 1649-1996 MSS 208
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Record Group IV: Horsford Family
  - Series A: Eben N. Horsford
    - Subseries 1: Correspondence
      - Subsubseries a: Family/General
        - Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, undated (Box 65, Folder 59)
        - Mutual Reserve Fund Life Association, 1887 (Box 65, Folder 60)
        - Henry W. Muzzy, 1874, 1877 (Box 65, Folder 61)
        - Isaac Myer, 1888 (Box 65, Folder 61)
        - J.J. Myers, 1886 (Box 65, Folder 62)
        - J.J. Myers, W.A. Munroe, Carles A. McIntyre and J.G. Thorp, 1890 (Box 65, Folder 64)
        - Charles Myne [?], 1887 (Box 65, Folder 65)
        - Brueder Nastopil, 1890 (Box 65, Folder 66)
        - Henry Neijnauer, 1889 (Box 65, Folder 67)
        - D. Nelson, 1841 (Box 65, Folder 68)
        - Mrs. J.H. Hudson Nevins, 1883 May 15 (Box 65, Folder 69)
        - New York and [?] Publishing Company, 1872 (Box 65, Folder 70)
        - New York Belting and Packing Company, 1871 (Box 65, Folder 71)
        - Emily Newcomb, undated (Box 65, Folder 72)
        - Herman H. Newell, 1831, 1835, undated (Box 65, Folder 73)
        - W.W. Newell, 1888 (Box 65, Folder 74)
        - John Newland, 1844 (Box 65, Folder 75)
        - Harry R. Nichols, 1889, undated (Box 65, Folder 76)
        - N. Nicolaysen, 1889 (Box 65, Folder 77)
        - S.B. Nicoll [L.B.?], 1872, 1874 (Box 65, Folder 78)
        - Hjalmar Nilsson, 1890 (Box 65, Folder 79)
        - Edmund Noble, 1887 (Box 65, Folder 80)
        - T.W. Norman, 1889 (Box 65, Folder 81)
        - C. North, 1839, 1840 (Box 65, Folder 82)
        - Mary North, 1843 (Box 65, Folder 83)
        - William North, 1838-1839 (Box 65, Folder 84)
        - C.E. Norton, 1881-1883, 1885, 1886, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Edith L. Norton, 1886-1889 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Elizabeth Norton, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - Harry L. Norton, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Henry Norton, 1837-1840 (Box 66, Folder 5)
        - Herman Norton, 1841 (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - Jane Norton, 1841 (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Julia Norton (cousin), undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - Lewis M. Norton, 1842 (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - Lewis M. Norton and Maria (cousins), 1840 (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - Lissy Norton, 1844 (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Lissy Norton and W.A. Norton, 1843-1844 (Box 66, Folder 12)
        - Lizzie N. [Norton], 1887 (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Maria Norton, 1839 January 19 (Box 66, Folder 14)
        - Mary Jane Norton, 1841 (Box 66, Folder 15)
        - Mr. Norton, undated (Box 66, Folder 16)
        - R. Norton, 1843 (Box 66, Folder 17)
        - Robert Norton, circa 1835 (Box 66, Folder 18)
        - Tom H. Noton, 1875-1890 (Box 66, Folder 19)
        - W.A. Norton (cousin), 1841-1844 (Box 66, Folder 20)
        - Wilbert Norton, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 21)
        - Sam C. Noteage, 1864 (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - Notman Photographic Company, 1887 (Box 66, Folder 23)
        - Numismatic and Antiquarian Society of Montreal, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 24)
        - Henry Nye, 1873 (Box 66, Folder 25)
        - James Oakey, 1838-1842, undated (Box 66, Folder 26)
        - Andrew K. Ober, 1888-1889 (Box 66, Folder 27)
        - to Fred A. Ober (last letter written by E.N. Horsford), 1892 (Box 66, Folder 28)
        - to Thomas Olcott, undated (Box 66, Folder 29)
        - J.P. Oliver, 1883, 1887 (Box 66, Folder 30)
        - O'Leary [?], 1842 (Box 66, Folder 31)
        - A.B. Olmstead, 1842 (Box 66, Folder 32)
        - Julius E. Olson, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 33)
        - Oneida Historical Society, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 34)
        - John W. Ordway, 1861 (Box 66, Folder 35)
        - D.C. Osborn, 1894 (Box 66, Folder 36)
        - John A. Ostbury, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 37)
        - Dr. Fessenden N. Otis, undated (Box 66, Folder 38)
        - Adolphe Ott, 1873 (Box 66, Folder 39)
        - E.P. (Chamberlain Vine and Studio), 1889 (Box 66, Folder 40)
        - J.D.P. (US Patent Office), 1868 (Box 66, Folder 41)
        - Pach Brothers Photographers, 1887 (Box 66, Folder 42)
        - A.S. Packard, 1888 (Box 66, Folder 43)
        - W.S. Packer, 1843 (Box 66, Folder 44)
        - Elias N. Paine, 1872 (Box 66, Folder 45)
        - Mrs. Robert Treat Paine, undated (Box 66, Folder 46)
        - Alice F. Palmer, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 47)
        - G.H. Palmer, 1889-1890 (Box 66, Folder 48)
        - Julius A. Palmer, 1864 (Box 66, Folder 49)
        - Edmund M. Parker, 1889, undated (Box 66, Folder 50)
        - G.F. Parker, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 51)
        - H.E. Parker, 1889-1890 (Box 66, Folder 52)
        - J. Eugene Parker, 1887, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 53)
        - F. Parkman, 1872, undated (Box 66, Folder 54)
        - C. Wellman Parks, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 55)
        - J.G. Parry [?], undated (Box 66, Folder 56)
        - S.H.H. Parsons, 1841 (Box 66, Folder 57)
        - H.S. Partridge, 1889 (Box 66, Folder 58)
        - George W. Patterson, 1837-1838, 1842-1843, 1875 (Box 66, Folder 59)
        - John Patterson (letter of recommendation for E.N. Horsford), 1844 (Box 66, Folder 60)
        - A.P. Peabody, 1887, 1889-1890 (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - Francis G. Peabody, 1886, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 2)
        - Peabody Museum of American Archaeology and Ethnology, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - I. Pearson, 1842 (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - Henry G. Pearson (NY Post Office), 1882 (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - Jonathan Pearson, 1842 (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Richard L. Pease, 1886 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - Emily W. Peck, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
        - M. Pegeot, 1845 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - O.B. Peirce [?] to Crittendon and E.N. Horsford, 1841 (Box 67, Folder 10)
        - William S. Pelletreau, 1881 (Box 67, Folder 11)
        - George Pellow, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 12)
        - George R. Perkins, 1843 (Box 67, Folder 13)
        - J.S. Perry, 1842 (Box 67, Folder 14)
        - John S. Perry, 1886-1889 (Box 67, Folder 15)
        - Johnny [Perry], 1844 (Box 67, Folder 16)
        - Perry Store Manufacturing Company, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 17)
        - Henrik G. Petersen, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 18)
        - Henry Phillips, Jr., 1887 (Box 67, Folder 19)
        - Edwards C. Pickering, 1886-887 (Box 67, Folder 20)
        - George W. Pierce, 1887, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 21)
        - J.M. Pierce, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 22)
        - Walter W. Pike, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 23)
        - Louis Pio, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 24)
        - William T. Piper, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 25)
        - A. Platt, 1841 (Box 67, Folder 26)
        - D. Bauder (Pleasant Valley Wine Company), 1882 (Box 67, Folder 27)
        - William Plumer, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 28)
        - Lucy A. Plympton, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 29)
        - Charles Poindexter, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 30)
        - A. Pollok, 1864-1868 (Box 67, Folder 31)
        - Thaddeus Pomeroy, 1841 (Box 67, Folder 32)
        - Alex S. Porter, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 33)
        - Edward Porter, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 34)
        - Edward F. Porter, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 35)
        - Thomas B. Porter (Cobden Club), 1889 (Box 67, Folder 36)
        - Postcards to E.N. Horsford [as originally grouped], 1889-1890 (Box 67, Folder 37)
        - Arthur Potter, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 38)
        - Thomas B. Potter (Cobden Club), 1887-1890 (Box 67, Folder 39)
        - J.M. Powell, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 40)
        - L.P. Powell, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 41)
        - Francis L. Pratt, 1887, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 42)
        - Henry H. Preston, 1886-1887 (Box 67, Folder 43)
        - to Jesse Preston, 1884-1885 (Box 67, Folder 44)
        - G.W. Prosch to Horsford & Cushman, 1841 (Box 67, Folder 45)
        - G.H. Prufeull [?], 1861 (Box 67, Folder 46)
        - James C. Pilling (Smithsonian Institution), 1887, 1889-1890 (Box 67, Folder 47)
        - F.W. Putnam, 1883, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 48)
        - G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1889, undated (Box 67, Folder 49)
        - Bernard A. Quaritch, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 50)
        - Josiah Quincy, 1848, 1850, 1861 (Box 67, Folder 51)
        - Louise Quincy [?], 1890 (Box 67, Folder 52)
        - Henry Race, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 53)
        - Benjamin Rand, 1887-1889 (Box 67, Folder 54)
        - Edward Rand, 1889-1890 (Box 67, Folder 55)
        - George Rand, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 56)
        - Hattie B. Rand, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 57)
        - Sarah M. Rand, undated (Box 67, Folder 58)
        - Silas Rand, 1888 (Box 67, Folder 59)
        - Ingebort Rasmussen, 1888, undated (Box 67, Folder 60)
        - E.W. Rathbone, undated (Box 67, Folder 61)
        - J.W.G. Rathbone, undated (Box 67, Folder 62)
        - Redwood Library, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 63)
        - S. Reed, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 64)
        - H. Reilly, 1846 (Box 67, Folder 65)
        - W. Bayard van Rensselaer, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 66)
        - Rensselear Polytechnic Institute, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 67)
        - Revell, undated (Box 67, Folder 68)
        - Henry Lee Reynolds, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 69)
        - Alexander H. Rice, 1886 (Box 67, Folder 70)
        - S. Richard, 1865 (Box 67, Folder 71)
        - Charles W. Richards, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 72)
        - Laurel Richards, undated (Box 67, Folder 73)
        - G.B. Richardson, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 74)
        - W.T. Richardson, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 75)
        - Sidney S. Rider, undated (Box 67, Folder 76)
        - Robert, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 77)
        - David C. Roberts, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 78)
        - C. Lockhart Robertson, 1877 (Box 67, Folder 79)
        - Susan P.B. Robins, undated (Box 67, Folder 80)
        - M. Robinson, 1842, 1844 (Box 67, Folder 81)
        - A. Rogers, 1841 (Box 67, Folder 82)
        - H. Rogers, 1837 (Box 67, Folder 83)
        - W.B. Rogers, 1838 (Box 67, Folder 84)
        - Henry Roneike, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 85)
        - Charles G. Root, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 86)
        - John C. Ropes, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Walter Rowlands, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Royal Society of Northern Antiquaries, 1888 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Rutgers College Library, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - A.H. Russell, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Alice Russell, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - William Russell, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - John Ryers, 1834 (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - S. [?], 1887 (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - F.S. [?], 1874 June 30 (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - F.W.S., 1888 (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - St. Paul Public Library, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - C.J. Salle, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - F.B. Sandborn, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 14)
        - Chester Sanger, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 15)
        - Warren Sanger, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 16)
        - John O. Sargent, 1861 (Box 68, Folder 17)
        - W.A. Saunders (re account of John Hicks in Lexington and Concord, 1775), 1871 (Box 68, Folder 18)
        - Scandinavian Chorus, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 19)
        - J.L. van Schoonheren, 1841 (Box 68, Folder 20)
        - to J.L. van Schoonheren, 1841 (Box 68, Folder 21)
        - Jackson S. Schultz, 1873 (Box 68, Folder 22)
        - B. Schwartz, undated (Box 68, Folder 23)
        - H. Schwarz, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 24)
        - J.A. Schwarzenberg, undated (Box 68, Folder 25)
        - H.W. Scott, 1838 (Box 68, Folder 26)
        - Herman Scott, 1833 (Box 68, Folder 27)
        - J. Alvin Scott, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 28)
        - Grace Scudder, 1888 (Box 68, Folder 29)
        - J.M. Sears, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 30)
        - C. Seaver, Jr, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 31)
        - to General See, 1864 (Box 68, Folder 32)
        - A.E. Serrell, 1843 (Box 68, Folder 33)
        - Henry D. Sewale, 1842-1846 (Box 68, Folder 34)
        - Henry Sewale and Eliza Horsford, 1843 (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - [J.] Sewall (cousin), 1844 (Box 68, Folder 36)
        - J.B. Sewall, 1887, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 37)
        - Alice Seward, undated (Box 68, Folder 38)
        - Seymour [?] (nephew), 1886, 1889, 1890 (Box 68, Folder 39)
        - Seymour [?], 1843 January 23 (Box 68, Folder 40)
        - Carrie Shanahan, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 41)
        - C.S. Shaw, 1844 (Box 68, Folder 42)
        - to Mrs. Shaw, undated (Box 68, Folder 43)
        - S.J. Shaw, 1842 November 14 (Box 68, Folder 44)
        - John Gilmary Shea, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 45)
        - Shelter Island Land Company, 1872 (Box 68, Folder 46)
        - S.O. Sherman, 1887 October 24 (Box 68, Folder 47)
        - W.G. Shillabert, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 48)
        - Tam Shin - Pacific Union Company, undated (Box 68, Folder 49)
        - Marie A. Shipley, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 50)
        - J.E. Shmohzun, 1874 (Box 68, Folder 51)
        - Moses Shuyer, 1887 May 4 (Box 68, Folder 52)
        - L.H. Sigourney, 1843 (Box 68, Folder 53)
        - John Siles, 1835 (Box 68, Folder 54)
        - B. Silliman, 1843, 1844, 1869 (Box 68, Folder 55)
        - E.W. Simontov, 1890 (Box 68, Folder 56)
        - Sam Sinclair, 1872 (Box 68, Folder 57)
        - Robert B. Sines (with enclosed letter from Lyman Bridges), 1873 September 18 (Box 68, Folder 58)
        - Benjamin H. Sisson, 1875 (Box 68, Folder 59)
        - Mrs. J.C. Skidmore, 1880 (Box 68, Folder 60)
        - Israel Slade, 1838-1839 (Box 68, Folder 61)
        - Israel Slade, 1839-1841 (Box 68, Folder 62)
        - William Sleight, 1885 (Box 68, Folder 63)
        - Sarah L'Hommedieu Slocum, 1884, 1885 [?] (Box 68, Folder 64)
        - A. K. Smiley, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 65)
        - Miss Smith, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 66)
        - B.F. Smith, 1843 (Box 68, Folder 67)
        - Clement L. Smith, 1887 (Box 68, Folder 68)
        - I. Lawrence Smith, 1843 (Box 68, Folder 69)
        - Louilla Smith, 1889 (Box 68, Folder 70)
        - R.V. Smith, 1886 (Box 68, Folder 71)
        - S.R. Smith to A. Crittenton, 1841 October 22 (Box 68, Folder 72)
        - R.L. Snow, 1887, undated (Box 68, Folder 73)
        - Joseph Soho, 1890 (Box 68, Folder 74)
        - William H. Spencer (M.T. Morris Self-Examining Society), 1836-1838, undated (Box 68, Folder 75)
        - Southold Savings Bank, 1875 May 15 (Box 68, Folder 76)
        - William H. Spencer, 1839 (Box 68, Folder 77)
        - William H. Spencer, 1839-1840 (Box 68, Folder 78)
        - William H. Spencer, 1840-1842 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - William H. Spencer, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - John B. Staats, 1841 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Mrs. Stanley, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Emily S. Stanley, 1837, 1838 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Harriet Stanley, 1836 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Harriet and Emily Stanley to Eliza and E.N. Horsford, 1836 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - A. Starbuck, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - State Library of Massachusetts, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - O. Steele, 1843 June 18 (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - A.W. Stevens, 1889-1890 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - John H. Stevens, 1888 (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Henry A. Stinson, 1886 (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Stone & Downer, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - George F. Stone, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - J.S. Stone, 1886 (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - Mary Tryon Stone, undated (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - J.J. Storrow, 1878 (Box 69, Folder 18)
        - R.S. Storrs, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 19)
        - Mary Fiske Stoughton, 1886 (Box 69, Folder 20)
        - Suffolk County Clerk, 1879 (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Suffolk Trust and Investment Co., 1888 January 17 (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - B. Sullivan, 1844 (Box 69, Folder 23)
        - A.C. Sully, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 24)
        - C.S. Sweetland, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 25)
        - Walter B. Swift, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 26)
        - William F. Swift, 1883 (Box 69, Folder 27)
        - Marie Tagerhuber to Dr. Arnstein, undated (Box 69, Folder 28)
        - Evelina Talbot, 1840 (Box 69, Folder 29)
        - Marion Talbot, undated (Box 69, Folder 30)
        - G.H. Talmend [?], undated (Box 69, Folder 31)
        - J.W. Taylor, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 32)
        - John Taylor, 1842 September 8 (Box 69, Folder 33)
        - V.O. Taylor, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 34)
        - J.R. Teele, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 35)
        - Telephone Despatch Company, 1880 (Box 69, Folder 36)
        - Stuart J. Terry, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 37)
        - J.B. Thayer, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 38)
        - J. Henry Thayer, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 39)
        - Carl Euyen Thiel, 1874 July 27 (Box 69, Folder 40)
        - G.D. Thiligny, 1840 (Box 69, Folder 41)
        - Harriet Thindale (cousin), 1838 May 5 (Box 69, Folder 42)
        - David N. Thomas, 1874 (Box 69, Folder 43)
        - J.G. Thompson, 1887, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 44)
        - S. Millett Thompson, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 45)
        - W.S. Thorpe, October 16, 1865 (Box 69, Folder 46)
        - Thursday Evening Club, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 47)
        - Charles H. Thurston, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 48)
        - Frank L. Tibbetts, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 49)
        - Tilden, Thurber and Company, 1887 April 25 (Box 69, Folder 50)
        - Jas. M. Tilser, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 51)
        - Tompkins, Gage and Perry, 1891 (Box 69, Folder 52)
        - William Wallace Tooker, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 53)
        - E. Tourjee, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 54)
        - Martin Townsend, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 55)
        - S. Toy, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 56)
        - Felix Tracy, 1841 (Box 69, Folder 57)
        - Treadwell & Co., 1887 November 4 (Box 69, Folder 58)
        - David Treadwell, 1860 (Box 69, Folder 59)
        - Trinity Historical Society, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 60)
        - Troy Young Men's Association, 1842 July 15 (Box 69, Folder 61)
        - Truebner and Co., 1889 September 17 (Box 69, Folder 62)
        - H. Hammond Trumbull, 1884, 1887 (Box 69, Folder 63)
        - Mary V. Tryon, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 64)
        - Thomas Tryon, 1886-1890, undated (Box 69, Folder 65)
        - J.H. Tuthill, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 66)
        - Julia Gardiner Tyler, 1884-1886 (Box 69, Folder 67)
        - Lyon G. Tyler, 1883 (Box 69, Folder 68)
        - F.S.U., undated (Box 69, Folder 69)
        - Dora Ulex, 1889, undated (Box 69, Folder 70)
        - University of Toronto Library, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 71)
        - US Navy Department, 1864 (Box 69, Folder 72)
        - US Patent Office, 1863 (Box 69, Folder 73)
        - to Valentine and Butler, 1864 (Box 69, Folder 74)
        - William J. Vaughn, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 75)
        - Joseph Vobe, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 76)
        - Mary C. Vorman, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 77)
        - P.D. van Vradenberg, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 78)
        - S.W., undated (Box 69, Folder 79)
        - William W., 1887 (Box 69, Folder 80)
        - M. Wadhams (from folder with Daniel Marsh), 1837-1839 (Box 69, Folder 81)
        - to C.C. Waite, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 82)
        - H.R. Waite (American Institute of Civics), 1887 (Box 69, Folder 83)
        - J.S. Walker, 1840-1842 (Box 69, Folder 84)
        - John S. Walker, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 85)
        - W.F. Walker, 1840 (Box 69, Folder 86)
        - William E. Wall, 1889 (Box 69, Folder 87)
        - F.T. Wallace, 1890 (Box 69, Folder 88)
        - Walmsley family (birth and death announcements), 1884 (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Waltham Public Library, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Henry A. Ward, 1861-1863, 1881-1883 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Ethelbert Warfield and Nellie Tilton, 1890 August 28 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - J. Warren, 1888, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Winslow Warren, 1892 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Charles Washburton, 1838 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - J.A. Washington, 1886 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - M.L. Watsen, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - to H. Watson (and reply), 1839 (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - to Miss Watson, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
        - Daniel Weathesheall, 1839 (Box 70, Folder 12)
        - H. Weidebusch, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 13)
        - James C. Welling, 1888 (Box 70, Folder 14)
        - David A. Wells, 1886-1887, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
        - David A. Wells, 1889, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
        - R.H. Wells, 1843 (Box 70, Folder 17)
        - Western Union (W.C. Humstone), 1887 (Box 70, Folder 18)
        - to Western Union Telegraph Co., 1887 (Box 70, Folder 19)
        - Horace Leslie Wheeler, 1890 (Box 70, Folder 20)
        - William Wheildon, 1889-1890 (Box 70, Folder 21)
        - Charles Whipple, 1837-1838 (Box 70, Folder 22)
        - Epher Whitaker, 1884-1889 (Box 70, Folder 23)
        - Horace White, 1887, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 24)
        - J.B. White, 1888 (Box 70, Folder 25)
        - John W. White, 1886-1887 (Box 70, Folder 26)
        - Henry Whitmore, undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Anne Whitney, undated (Box 70, Folder 28)
        - H.I.M. Whitney, undated (Box 70, Folder 29)
        - Henry A. Whitney, 1886 (Box 70, Folder 30)
        - John F. Whitney, 1889-1890, undated (Box 70, Folder 31)
        - Sarah F. Whiting, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 32)
        - W.C. Whitney to H. Weld Fuller (with documents re Lt. Col. Broome), 1887 July 20 (Box 70, Folder 33)
        - W.D. Whitney, 1887 (Box 70, Folder 34)
        - J.G. Whittier (empty envelope), 1884 (Box 70, Folder 35)
        - Wickany [?], 1889 (Box 70, Folder 36)
        - William Wickham, 1873-1874 (Box 70, Folder 37)
        - Julius Wiesner, 1874 (Box 70, Folder 38)
        - Dr. H. Will, 1846 (Box 70, Folder 39)
        - [M.?] William, 1874 (Box 70, Folder 40)
        - Annie H. Williams, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 41)
        - Clarence H. Williams, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 42)
        - Mr. Williamson (University College), undated (Box 70, Folder 43)
        - Edward Willis, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 44)
        - Marcius Willson, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 45)
        - A.M. Willson, 1834, 1883 (Box 70, Folder 46)
        - Mrs. A.M. Wilson, 1834, 1839 (Box 70, Folder 47)
        - Daniel Wilson, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 48)
        - John Wilson and son, 1886-1887, 1889-1890 (Box 70, Folder 49)
        - H.A. Wiltse, 1837-1838 (Box 70, Folder 50)
        - S.C. Wiltse, 1836-1837 (Box 70, Folder 51)
        - Ada G. Wing, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 52)
        - William C. Winslow, 1887-1888 (Box 70, Folder 53)
        - Constance Winsor, 1887, undated (Box 70, Folder 54)
        - Justin Winsor, 1882-1887 (Box 70, Folder 55)
        - John Winthrop (Lenox Club), 1889 (Box 70, Folder 56)
        - R.C. Winthrop, 1884-1889 (Box 70, Folder 57)
        - R.C. Winthrop, Jr. (memo re state of "Innocence"), undated (Box 70, Folder 58)
        - L.W. Wix, 1887 (Box 70, Folder 59)
        - Henry Wize, 1873 (Box 70, Folder 60)
        - William J. Wollman, 1890 (Box 70, Folder 61)
        - B. Wood, 1841-1842 (Box 70, Folder 62)
        - Frank Wood, 1887 (Box 70, Folder 63)
        - Levi Woodhouse, 1886 (Box 70, Folder 64)
        - James Woodrow, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 65)
        - George Wright, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 66)
        - Henry Wurtz, 1868 (Box 70, Folder 67)
        - Elizabeth Wyman, undated (Box 70, Folder 68)
        - Morrell Wyman, 1884 (Box 70, Folder 69)
        - Jos van den Wyngaert, 1875, 1886-1890 (Box 70, Folder 70)
        - Alexander Young, 1889-1890 (Box 70, Folder 71)
        - Edward J. Young, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 72)
        - Dr. Zamminer (letter of recommendation for E.N. Horsford), 1846 (Box 70, Folder 73)
        - E. Zerdahebyi, undated (Box 70, Folder 74)
        - Heinrich Zlihy, 1873, 1889 (Box 70, Folder 75)
        - Unknown, 1842 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Unknown (French), 1870 November 24 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Unknown (German), 1873 September 13 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Unknown (unidentified language), 1873 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Unknown (German), 1874 September 28 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - Unknown (note on envelope), 1884 (Box 71, Folder 6)
        - Unknown, 1889 August 31 (Box 71, Folder 7)